Stop dreaming. Start living.
The Secret Life of Walter Mitty is a adventure,
comedy, drama film directed by Ben Stiller.
A timid magazine photo manager who lives life vicariously through daydreams
embarks on a true-life adventure when a negative goes missing.
Walter Mitty, played by Ben Stiller.
Cheryl Melhoff, played by Kristen Wiig.
Sean O'Connell, played by Sean Penn.
Edna Mitty, played by Shirley MacLaine.
Ted Hendricks, played by Adam Scott.
Odessa Mitty, played by Kathryn Hahn.
The Secret Life of Walter Mitty is a 2013 adventure comedy-drama film directed,
co-produced by and starring Ben Stiller and written by Steve Conrad.
The film also stars Kristen Wiig, Shirley MacLaine,
Adam Scott, Kathryn Hahn, and Sean Penn.
Though "more of a remake" of the 1947 film of the same name, both are
film adaptations of James Thurber's 1939 short story.
It follows a maladaptive daydreamer named Walter Mitty on his quest to find a missing negative
print and its elusive photojournalist for Life magazine's final print issue.
Following a tumultuous production hell that spanned multiple studios, directors and leading actors dating back to 1994, it finally
found traction in 2011 with Stiller as director and star of the film under 20th Century Fox and Samuel Goldwyn Films.
The film premiered at the New York Film Festival on October 5, 2013, and was theatrically released on December 25, 2013, in North America to
generally mixed reception, with praise for Stiller's direction, cinematography, and its soundtrack featuring José González.
It was chosen by the National Board of Review as
one of the top ten films of 2013.
The film explores themes of himalaya mountain range,
photographer, iceland, daydream, magazine.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.